{
   "enRounds": [
      {
         "id": "1",
         "nums": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9", "10"],
         "title": "Quotes",
         "questions": [
            {
               "id": "1",
               "question": "Which movie is this quote from: ",
               "quote": "You know how to fight six men, we can teach you how to engage six hundred.",
               "answer": ["Batman Begins"]
            },
            {
               "id": "2",
               "question": "Which movie is this quote from: ",
               "quote": "Look at the stars. The great kings of the past look down on us from those stars.",
               "answer": ["The Lion King"]
            },
            {
               "id": "3",
               "question": "Which movie is this quote from: ",
               "quote": "Get busy living, or get busy dying.",
               "answer": ["Shawshank Redemption"]
            },
            {
               "id": "4",
               "question": "Which movie is this quote from: ",
               "quote": "To infinity and beyond!",
               "answer": ["Toy Story"]
            },
            {
               "id": "5",
               "question": "Which movie is this quote from: ",
               "quote": "Carpe diem. Seize the day, boys.",
               "answer": ["Dead Poets Society"]
            },
            {
               "id": "6",
               "question": "Fill in the missing word from the quote:",
               "task": "Life is like a box of __________. You never know what you've gonna get.",
               "quote": "Life is like a box of chocolates. You never know what you've gonna get.",
               "answer": "Forrest Gump"
            },
            {
               "id": "7",
               "question": "Fill in the missing word from the quote:",
               "task": ["- It's all so magical.", "- Yeah", "It's a shame __________ had to miss this.", "Nah, he hates fireworks. He doesn't really like flying either."],
               "quote": ["- It's all so magical.", "- Yeah", "It's a shame Abou had to miss this.", "Nah, he hates fireworks. He doesn't really like flying either."],
               "answer": "Aladdin"
            },
            {
               "id": "8",
               "question": "Fill in the missing word from the quote:",
               "task": "Give me the __________ and take the money.",
               "quote": "Give me the phone and take the money.",
               "answer": "The Gentlemen"
            },
            {
               "id": "9",
               "question": "Fill in the missing word from the quote:",
               "task": ["I'm required to tell you by law... I'm a Jew.", "Well, I'm a __________. So there we are."],
               "quote": ["I'm required to tell you by law... I'm a Jew.", "Well, I'm a German. So there we are."],
               "answer": "Schindler's List"
            },
            {
               "id": "10",
               "question": "Fill in the missing word from the quote:",
               "task": "I like the way you __________, boy.",
               "quote": "I like the way you die, boy.",
               "answer": "Django Unchained"
            }
         ]
      },
      {
         "id": "2",
         "title": "Trivia",
         "questions": [
            {
                "id": "1",
                "question": "How many times did Sean Bean die in his movies throughout his career?",
                "answer": "2023"
            }
         ]
      }
    ]
}
